ishotspot.com 2009-12-28

# IsHotSpot.com - Free Image Hosting

|    | 

IsHotSpot.com Privacy Policy  
  
---|---  
  |  IsHotSpot.com is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. Should you choose to provide your Email address or any other personal information on any of the forms found on our site, you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with IsHotSpot.com. This privacy policy is intended for all users of IsHotSpot.com.  
By visiting this web site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services.  
  
  |  If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact IsHotSpot.com at admin@IsHotSpot.com.  
  |  Information Collection   
  |  IsHotSpot.com is the sole owner of the information collected on our site. IsHotSpot.com collects and monitors information from our users at several different points on our Web site. Unless you opt-out, you give IsHotSpot.com permission to use your information as per this privacy policy.  
While IsHotSpot.com will make every effort possible to protect your privacy, we do not promise, nor should you expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. This will include parties who attempt to illegally enter our web site and intercept or access transmissions or private communications.  
Unless described otherwise in this privacy policy, we will not sell any information. All information collected will be used solely by IsHotSpot.com to deliver targeted newsletters and advertisements.  
  |  Information Use   
  |  We store information that we collect through cookies, log files and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user¡¯s visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties, unless specifically mentioned in this agreement.  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user¡¯s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user¡¯s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.  
We have no control over any third party use also use cookies to store personal information. However, we do not provide this information to any third party.  
Like most standard Web site servers we may use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user¡¯s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
  |  Information Sharing   
  |  Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. This includes, but is not limited to, any defense to any claim in which IsHotSpot.com is a defendant, to assist in any investigations by law enforcement agencies, or violations of any IsHotSpot.com policy.  
  |  Notification of Changes   
  |  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.   
  |  Contact Information   
  |  If users have any questions, disputes or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at admin@IsHotSpot.com.
